{
  "questions": [
    {
        "question": "Which company developed SQL?",
        "correctAnswer": "IBM",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "Oracle",
            "Microsoft"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? A Primary Key is required for a table.",
        "correctAnswer": "False",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which SQL statement is used to extract data from a database?",
        "correctAnswer": "SELECT",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "GET",
            "EXTRACT"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a SQL statement?",
        "correctAnswer": "DESTROY TABLE",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "DELETE",
            "DROP TABLE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The S in SQL stands for which of the following?",
        "correctAnswer": "Structured",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "Standardized",
            "Sequential"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the underscore represent in a LIKE statement?",
        "correctAnswer": "Single Character",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "Wildcard Character",
            "Lowercase Character"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? The ORDER BY statement is executed before the GROUP BY statement.",
        "correctAnswer": "False",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The JOIN statement defaults to which of the following?",
        "correctAnswer": "INNER JOIN",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "LEFT JOIN",
            "FULL JOIN"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which SQL statement is used to create an alias?",
        "correctAnswer": "AS",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "ALIAS",
            "CREATE"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "An alias cannot be made for which of the following?",
        "correctAnswer": "Database",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "Table",
            "Column"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a SQL function?",
        "correctAnswer": "MID",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "MIN",
            "MAX"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it true that SQL can only be used for relational databases?",
        "correctAnswer": "Yes",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "No"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a SQL operator?",
        "correctAnswer": "NOT",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "NOR",
            "NIL"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "True or False? UNION ALL is a SQL operator.",
        "correctAnswer": "True",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The EXISTS operator checks for which of the following?",
        "correctAnswer": "Existence of a record in a subquery",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "Existence of a database given a parameter"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a SQL function?",
        "correctAnswer": "NOTNULL",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "ISNULL",
            "IFNULL"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which SQL statement is used to return only different values?",
        "correctAnswer": "SELECT DISTINCT",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "SELECT UNIQUE",
            "SELECT DIFFERENT"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which SQL keyword is used to sort the result?",
        "correctAnswer": "ORDER BY",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "SORT BY",
            "SORT"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is not a DDL statement?",
        "correctAnswer": "Delete",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "Truncate",
            "Alter"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which operator is used to select values within a range?",
        "correctAnswer": "BETWEEN",
        "tags": [
            "SQL"
        ],
        "wrongAnswer": [
            "WITHIN",
            "RANGE"
        ]
    } 
  ]
}
